Thank you everybody. I personally from the bottom of my heart would like to
thank everyone
here for your presence this evening among other inductees. Unlike Jose said,
God is first
on my list of thanks and then comes my parents and he mentioned my parents
which were very
mental in my life. Pretty van grossa Maria, who are now these kids, may they
rest in peace.
Who taught me everything from early childhood that service to others is the
most important
thing to do in our lifetime. Our homeless will of faith and love, joy and care
and compassion
for others. We have families passing through the city that needed a place to
stay and our
home became that place. It was a house full of most of the time among with our
pets. It
was like a suit. I would like to thank all the people that helped me through my
illness
which Jose mentioned. From a traumatic brain injury on May 21st will be 10
years in 2008.
An angry reason that almost took my life. I want to thank my siblings present
here for
your undaunted love and support during that time and to this day I love you and
gracias
and I would like my siblings to stand wherever you are. My brothers and sisters.
Gracias for being here. I want to thank all my dedicated friends that I have
had all these
years. Too many to count. I want to thank my sisters and community that their
many
consistence and associties of peace for your continued support in all the
ministries I
took on. Thank you. There are some sisters with me here tonight. Please stay.
[applause]
Lastly I would like to thank Deborah Henson and the Cleveland International
Hall of Fame
and Dan for all you did to give me here and you continue to do for others that
will come
after us. May you all have a safe trip back home. May the peace of our gracious
God go
with you.
[applause]
I got Sister Alicia, I got an email from her saying, you know, I'm expecting to
see Sister
Rachel and all that here, you know, and she sent me an email saying, I got my
outfit,
I've got a flower for my hair, I've got a clumsy skirt, so if I'm dancing, it'll
move
with me.
[laughter]
[applause]